{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_24","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346222366","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346222366"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.clo.hear::story_25","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346227520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346227520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346237455","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346237455"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_O-M-N"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346241719","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346241719"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-K-B"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346249639","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346249639"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-F-J"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346256010","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346256010"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_J-S-M"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346282181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346282180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_CH-P-M"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346292844","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346292844"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-L-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" F"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346298135","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346298135"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_M-L-F"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346304635","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346304635"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_B-M-P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346308977","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346308977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_H-M-O"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346311958","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346311957"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_D-W-M"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" W"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346317352","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346317352"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_D-W-M"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346327288","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346327288"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_M_K-CH-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" M"," userResponse":" M"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346333080","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346333078"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" BPOP_M_K-CH-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346358477","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346358477"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_M_K-CH-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL3.incr.6","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346370960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346370960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_M_K-CH-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.uc:M..M.all.rand.all.stat.noShow.52","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346380013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346380012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 56d5d2a6-1609-40b2-8056-f4da948d6aed"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.ltr.uc_M..M.all.rand.all.stat.show.51"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_M_K-CH-M"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346389577","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346389576"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAPO"," userResponse":" HAPO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346390213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346390213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZAMANI"," userResponse":" ZAMANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346390457","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346390456"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346390982","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346390982"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KALE"," userResponse":" KALE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346392331","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346392328"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PALIKUWA"," userResponse":" PALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346392562","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346392562"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346393066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346393066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346394091","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346394090"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYEKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIYEKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346395133","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346395132"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKITEMBEA"," userResponse":" AKITEMBEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346396162","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346396162"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Hapo zamani za kale palikuwa na mtu aliyekuwa akitembea kichakani."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KICHAKANI"," userResponse":" KICHAKANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346398693","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346398692"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346399978","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346399977"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUTANA"," userResponse":" ALIKUTANA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346400181","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346400180"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346400744","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346400744"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ghafla alikutana na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346404245","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346404244"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346404941","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346404941"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346406402","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346406401"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIPUMZIKA"," userResponse":" AKIPUMZIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346406962","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346406961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KATIKA"," userResponse":" KATIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346407425","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346407425"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NYASI"," userResponse":" NYASI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346408119","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346408118"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FUPI"," userResponse":" FUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346408647","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346408646"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ZA"," userResponse":" ZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346409371","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346409370"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MSIMU"," userResponse":" MSIMU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346409484","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346409484"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WA"," userResponse":" WA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346410237","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346410237"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alikuwa akipumzika katika nyasi fupi za msimu wa baridi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BARIDI"," userResponse":" BARIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346413574","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346413574"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAKUTANO"," userResponse":" MAKUTANO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346414223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346414223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HAYO"," userResponse":" HAYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346415322","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346415322"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YALITOKEA"," userResponse":" YALITOKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346415961","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346415961"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" GHAFLA"," userResponse":" GHAFLA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346416785","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346416785"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346417298","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346417298"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HUYO"," userResponse":" HUYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346417897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346417896"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ASIJUE"," userResponse":" ASIJUE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346418066","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346418066"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LA"," userResponse":" LA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346418731","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346418731"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Makutano hayo yalitokea ghafla mtu huyo asijue la kufanya."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUFANYA"," userResponse":" KUFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346421793","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346421792"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJAWA"," userResponse":" ALIJAWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346422054","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346422054"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346422768","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346422767"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alijawa na woga."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOGA"," userResponse":" WOGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346426344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346426344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWANZONI"," userResponse":" MWANZONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346427151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346427151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346428534","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346428534"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISHANGAA"," userResponse":" ALISHANGAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346429492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346429492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" PIA"," userResponse":" PIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346430063","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346430063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346430862","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346430862"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346431507","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346431507"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwanzoni Simba alishangaa pia na kuogopa kidogo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KIDOGO"," userResponse":" KIDOGO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346434261","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346434261"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346435435","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346435435"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MNGURUMO"," userResponse":" MNGURUMO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346436079","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346436079"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MKUBWA"," userResponse":" MKUBWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346437380","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346437379"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULISIKIKA"," userResponse":" ULISIKIKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346437895","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346437895"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346438555","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346438555"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TUMBONI"," userResponse":" TUMBONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346439059","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346439059"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWAKE"," userResponse":" MWAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346439833","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346439832"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWANI"," userResponse":" KWANI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346440685","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346440684"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346440951","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346440950"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346441987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346441986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mngurumo mkubwa ulisikika kutoka tumboni mwake kwani alikuwa na njaa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 10"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NJAA"," userResponse":" NJAA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346444818","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346444816"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346445369","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346445369"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346446520","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346446519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIKUTA"," userResponse":" ALIJIKUTA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346447013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346447012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346447160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346447159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346447715","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346447715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346448260","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346448259"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alijikuta juu ya mti mrefu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MREFU"," userResponse":" MREFU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346451049","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346451048"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346451889","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346451888"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUPIGA"," userResponse":" KUPIGA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346452615","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346452615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Alianza kupiga mayowe."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MAYOWE"," userResponse":" MAYOWE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346455771","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346455770"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346456724","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346456723"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346457319","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346457319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" CHINI"," userResponse":" CHINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346457403","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346457403"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YA"," userResponse":" YA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346457917","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346457917"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTI"," userResponse":" MTI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346459035","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346459034"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKISUBIRI"," userResponse":" AKISUBIRI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346459595","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346459595"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alilala chini ya mti akisubiri mlo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346461944","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346461943"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346462969","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346462969"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ULIPOZIDI"," userResponse":" ULIPOZIDI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346463600","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346463600"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWENDA"," userResponse":" KWENDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346464528","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346464527"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346465800","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346465798"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIJIFANYA"," userResponse":" ALIJIFANYA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346466537","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346466536"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346467820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346467818"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda ulipozidi kwenda Simba alijifanya kulala usingizi ."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346470702","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346470701"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MUDA"," userResponse":" MUDA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346471257","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346471256"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MFUPI"," userResponse":" MFUPI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346471960","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346471960"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" BAADAYE"," userResponse":" BAADAYE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346473032","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346473031"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346473519","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346473519"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346474646","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346474645"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALILALA"," userResponse":" ALILALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346475878","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346475878"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Muda mfupi baadaye mtu yule alilala usingizi."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USINGIZI"," userResponse":" USINGIZI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346478438","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346478438"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KISHA"," userResponse":" KISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346479372","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346479371"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKAAMKA"," userResponse":" AKAAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346479835","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346479834"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kisha akaamka tena."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" TENA"," userResponse":" TENA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346482721","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346482720"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWISHONI"," userResponse":" MWISHONI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346484320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346484319"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISINZIA"," userResponse":" ALISINZIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346484579","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346484578"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346485470","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346485469"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULALA"," userResponse":" KULALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346486873","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346486873"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mwishoni alisinzia na kulala fofofo."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" FOFOFO"," userResponse":" FOFOFO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346490586","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346490586"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" LAKINI"," userResponse":" LAKINI"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346491064","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346491063"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MARA"," userResponse":" MARA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346492584","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346492584"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIPOROMOKA"," userResponse":" ALIPOROMOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346493117","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346493117"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUTOKA"," userResponse":" KUTOKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346493521","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346493520"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" JUU"," userResponse":" JUU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346494111","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346494111"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346495348","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346495347"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUMWANGUKIA"," userResponse":" KUMWANGUKIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346495761","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346495761"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346496233","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346496233"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346497213","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346497213"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Lakini mara aliporomoka kutoka juu na kumwangukia yule Simba aliyelala."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIYELALA"," userResponse":" ALIYELALA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346500414","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346500414"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WOTE"," userResponse":" WOTE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346501368","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346501367"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WALIAMKA"," userResponse":" WALIAMKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346501920","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346501919"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKIWA"," userResponse":" WAKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346503174","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346503174"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," userResponse":" WAMECHANGANYIKIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346503716","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346503715"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346504616","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346504615"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Wote waliamka wakiwa wamechanganyikiwa na kuogopa."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUOGOPA"," userResponse":" KUOGOPA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346507223","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346507223"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346508215","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346508215"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALISAHAU"," userResponse":" ALISAHAU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346508669","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346508668"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MLO"," userResponse":" MLO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346509200","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346509199"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346509820","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346509819"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346511486","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346511485"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBILIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBILIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346512533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346512533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" USALAMA"," userResponse":" USALAMA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346512967","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346512967"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Simba alisahau mlo wake na kukimbilia usalama wake."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346515735","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346515734"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MTU"," userResponse":" MTU"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346516344","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346516344"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" YULE"," userResponse":" YULE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346517447","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346517444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIANZA"," userResponse":" ALIANZA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346518413","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346518413"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUKIMBIA"," userResponse":" KUKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346519398","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346519397"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIELEKEA"," userResponse":" AKIELEKEA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346519931","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346519931"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" UPANDE"," userResponse":" UPANDE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346520445","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346520444"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MMOJA"," userResponse":" MMOJA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346520608","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346520607"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346521151","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346521151"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Mtu yule alianza kukimbia akielekea upande mmoja na Simba."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346523983","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346523983"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIGUNDUA"," userResponse":" ALIGUNDUA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346524500","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346524499"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWAMBA"," userResponse":" KWAMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346525292","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346525289"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIKUWA"," userResponse":" ALIKUWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346526177","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346526176"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" AKIKIMBIA"," userResponse":" AKIKIMBIA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346526362","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346526361"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346526882","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346526882"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Aligundua kwamba alikuwa akikimbia na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346529525","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346529524"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KWA"," userResponse":" KWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346530029","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346530028"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" HIVYO"," userResponse":" HIVYO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346531110","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346531108"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" ALIBADILISHA"," userResponse":" ALIBADILISHA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346531728","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346531727"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 3"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" MWELEKEO"," userResponse":" MWELEKEO"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346532354","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346532354"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 4"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" WAKE"," userResponse":" WAKE"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346532847","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346532847"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 5"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346533813","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346533813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 6"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KUEPUKA"," userResponse":" KUEPUKA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346534326","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346534326"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 7"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" KULIWA"," userResponse":" KULIWA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346534501","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346534500"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 8"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NA"," userResponse":" NA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346534987","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346534986"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::story_26","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346537533","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346537533"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346537593","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346537593"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" 630976ec-5bbe-4cb5-866d-28d5c1524815"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.hear__story_26"," matrixName":" stories"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Kwa hivyo alibadilisha mwelekeo wake na kuepuka kuliwa na Simba!"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 9"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" SIMBA"," userResponse":" SIMBA"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346573814","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346573813"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_M_E"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346580471","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346580471"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_R_M_E"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346587160","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346587159"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_J_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346594632","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346594632"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_J_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346605071","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346605071"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_J_CH"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346611250","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346611250"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_G_M_H"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" MID"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346617897","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346617897"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_W_R_M"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346624563","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346624561"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_U_W_M"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" RIGHT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346631222","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346631221"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_M_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346638698","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346638698"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_M_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346649095","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346649094"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_D_M_P"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346655320","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346655318"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_O_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346662808","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346662808"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_O_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346673265","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346673265"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_M_O_E"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" LEFT"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346679492","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346679492"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_M_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346686965","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346686965"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_M_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346697420","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346697420"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" o1_O_M_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" MID"," userResponse":" RIGHT"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"akira:all.ltr.uc:M..M.all.10.rand.say.27","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"1548346706013","data":{"timestamp":" 1548346706012"," userId":" 5B12002999"," sessionId":" 5B12002999_20190124_190937"," gameId":" c929a5a9-fcd3-4d3e-a008-6f5f4991e4f1"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" akira"," tutorId":" akira_all.ltr.uc_M..M.all.10.rand.say.27"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" o1_O_M_V"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}